Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Papers AIA.031.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: General, 1806-2011; 14 boxes
  - Grass Roots International Folk Resource Directory, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Green Linnet Records: Catalogs (folder one), 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Green Linnet Records: Catalogs (folder two), 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Green Linnet Records: Correspondence (folder one), 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Green Linnet Records: Correspondence (folder two), 1983-1993, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Green Linnet Records: Correspondence (folder three), undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Green Linnet Records: Financial (folder three), 1977-1985 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Green Linnet Records: Financial (folder two), 1986-1991 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Green Linnet Records: Financial (folder three), 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Green Linnet Records: Financial (folder four), 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Green Linnet Records: General (folder one), 1980-1988 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Green Linnet Records: General (folder two), 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Green Linnet Survey Cards, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Green Linnet Records: Press, 1979-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Humor, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Immigration and Ethnicity, 1977-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Innisfree Records (Green Linnet): Correspondence, 1977-c.1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Innisfree Records (Green Linnet): General, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Cultural Ecology, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Instruments: Banjo, 1898-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Instruments: Banjo: Jokes, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Instruments: Concertina, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Instruments: Dealers, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Instruments: Fiddle, 1973-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Instruments: Guitar, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Instruments: Harp (folder one), 1976-1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Instruments: Harp (folder two), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Instruments: Mandolin, 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Instruments: Tin Whistle, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Instruments: Uilleann Pipes, 1974-1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International House: Ethnic Festival Reports (folder one), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - International House: Ethnic Festival Reports (folder two), 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - International House: Ethnic Festival Reports (folder three), 1981, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - International House: Ethnic Festival Reports (folder four), undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - International House: Ethnic Festival Reports (folder five), undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - International House: Folklife Center, 1979-1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - International House: General (folder one), 1978-1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - International House: General (folder two), 1991-1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - International House: Grant Proposals, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - International House: Performer Contacts, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - International House: Trustee-Related (folder one), 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - International House: Trustee-Related (folder two), 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - International Village Fair: Budget (folder one), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - International Village (folder two), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - International Village Fair: Budget (folder three) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - International Village Fair: Crafts, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - International Village Fair: General (folder one), 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - International Village Fair: General (folder two), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - International Village Fair: General (folder three), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Internet, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Irish-American Benefits, 1990-1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Irish-American Cultural Institute, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Irish American Cultural Organizations, 1955-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Irish Arts Center, 1976-2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Irish Echo: Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Irish Film, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Irish History: Carribbean, 1932, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Irish in America: Long Journey Home (documentary), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Irish Language, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Irish Literary Supplement, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Irish Music: Baltimore, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Irish Music: Boston, 1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Irish Music: California (folder one), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Irish Music: California (folder two), 1993-1998, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Irish Music: Chicago (folder one), 1955-1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Irish Music: Chicago (folder two), 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Irish Music: Cleveland, 1979-1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Irish Music: Competitions, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Irish Music: Event Calendars, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Irish Music: Festivals (folder one), 1976-1991 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Irish Music: Festivals (folder two), 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Irish Music: Festivals (folder three), 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Irish Music: Festivals (folder four), 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Irish Music: Festivals (folder five), undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Irish Music: General, 1971-2000 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Irish Music: Journals (folder one), 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Irish Music: Journals (folder two), 1981-1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Irish Music: Michigan, 1977, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Irish Music: Missouri, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Irish Music: New Orleans, 1981, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Irish Music: New York, 1990-1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Irish Music: Pennsylvania, 1955-1998 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Irish Music: Pubs, 1984-1998 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Irish Music: Radio, 1985-1994 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Irish Music: Rock, Rap, 1978-1995 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Irish Music: San Francisco, late 1970s (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Irish Music: Washington D.C., 1978-1999 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Irish Music: Wisconsin, c.1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Irish Music: Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Irish Music in American: Bibliography, c. 1978 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Irish Musicians' Association of America, 1956-1976 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Irish Musicians' Association of America, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Irish Musicians: Addresses, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Irish: Spirituality, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Irish Tenors, 1977, 1990-2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Irish Traditional Music Archive, 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Jokebook: Muldoon's Jokes, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Journals: Dal gCais, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Journals: Folk Music Scene, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Journals: Force 10, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Journals: Keltica, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Journals: Sliab Luacra, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Journals: Sliab Luacra (folder two), 1987, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Journals: Sliab Luacra (folder three), 1991, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy Center Performing Arts Series, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Library of Congress: Ethnic Recordings in America, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Logo Songs Limited (Transatlantic), 1982-1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Longwood Gardens, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Magazines: Black Sheep Review, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Magazines: Creation Spirituality, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Magazines: Dirty Linen, 1993, 1994, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Magazines: Frets, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Magazines: Ireland, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Magazines: Irish America, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Magazines: Irish Illustrated, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Magazines Irish Music (folder one), 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Magazines: Irish Music (folder two), 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Magazines: Living Tradition, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Magazines: Old-Time Herald, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Magazines: Treoir (folder one), 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Magazines: Treoir (folder two) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Mailing Lists, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Milwaukee Irish Fest (folder one), 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Milwaukee Irish Fest (folder two), 1990-2005 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Milwaukee Irish Fest (folder three), undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Montana, 1989-1994 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Montserrat: General, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Montserrat: History, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Montserrat: Materials, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Morning Star Recording Studios, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mountain Heritage Center, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Music Publishing (including ASCAP and BMI), 1979-1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - National Assembly of Local Arts Agencies, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - National Council for the Traditional Arts: General, 1980-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - National Council for the Traditional Arts: Youngstown, OH. Assessment, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Best of Irish Music and Dance (folder one), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Best of Irish Music and Dance (folder two), 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Best of Irish Music and Dance: Final Report (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Consulting, 1984-1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: General, 1982-1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Grant Proposals, Correspondence., 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Heritage Tour (folder one), 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Heritage Tour (folder two), 1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Tour, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - National Heritage Fellowship Award, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - National Heritage Fellowship Awards: Program (folder one), 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - National Heritage Fellowship Awards: Program (folder two), 1990-2007 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - New Grove Dictionary of Music and Musicians, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - New Jersey Folk Festival, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters: Celtic Associations (folder one), 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Newsletters: Celtic Associations (folder two), 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Newsletters: Celtic Associations (folder three), 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Newsletters: Celtic Associations (folder four), 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Newsletters: Celtic Associations (folder five), 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Newsletters: Folk, 1981-1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings (folder one), 1981-1993 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings (folder two), 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings (folder three), 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings (folder four), undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Gaelic-American (folder one), 1903-1904 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Gaelic-American (folder two), 1904-1905 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Gaelic-American (folder three), 1905-1909 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Gaelic-American (folder four), 1910-1912 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Gaelic-American (folder five), 1911-1912 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Gaelic-American (folder six), 1920-1929 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Gaelic-American (folder seven), 1930-1935 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Irish American (Oversized), 1953 (Box Shared Tamiment 142, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Irish Echo (Oversized), 1944 (Box Shared Tamiment 142, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Irish World (Oversized), 1953, 1958, 1975 (Box Shared Tamiment 142, Folder 5)
  - New York Clipper (folder one), 1893 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - New York Clipper (folder two), 1895 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - New York Clipper (folder three), 1900 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - New York Clipper (folder four), 1900 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - New York Folklore Society, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - New York State Council on the Arts (folder one), 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - New York State Council on the Arts (folder two), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Nimbus Records, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - North Carolina Quadricentennial, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Oireachtais Report on Traditional Irish Music, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Out of Ireland (Documentary) (folder one), 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Out of Ireland (Documentary): Scripts and Drafts, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Omega Institute, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Package Tours (folder one), 1991-1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Package Tours (folder two), 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Package Tours (folder three), undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Package Tours: Smithsonian Institution, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Package Tours: Questionnaires (folder one), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Package Tours: Questionnaires (folder two), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Package Tours: Questionnaires (folder four), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Pamphlets: Irish and Irish-American History (folder one), 1946, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Pamphlets: Irish and Irish-American History (folder two), 1974, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Pennsylvania Council for the Arts, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Pennsylvania Folklife Advisory Council, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Pennsylvania: Media Contact Lists, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Performer Bios, 1975-1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Performing Ideas, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Pew Fellowships, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Philadelphia: General, 1931-1932, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group (folder one), 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group (folder two), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group (folder three), 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group (folder four), 1985-1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group (folder five), 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group (folder six), undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Folklore Project, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia: Irish Musicians' Union, Local No. 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Pilgrimages, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Poets and Poetry (folder one), c. 1860, 1980-2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Poets and Poetry (folder two), undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Project Children, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Promoters, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Radio, 1948, 1980-2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Radio Telefis Eireann (RTE): Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Budgets and Proposals (folder one), 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Budgets and Proposals (folder two), 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Correspondence (folder one), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Correspondence (folder two), 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Correspondence (folder three), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Drafts (folder one), undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Drafts (folder two), undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: Drafts (folder three), undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - RTE: Green Fields of America Series: General, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - RTE: Long Notes, 1979-1985 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - RTE: Long Note, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - RTE: Sounds Traditional Radio Series, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Recipes, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Recording Projects: Eddie Clarke and Joe Ryan, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Recording Projects: Flax in Bloom: Brendan Mulvihill, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Recording Projects: Irish Music from the East Coast, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Recording Projects: Irish Music, the Living Tradition, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Recording Projects: Irish Tradition, 1979/1980 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Recording Projects: Light Through the Leaves, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Recording Projects: Own Record, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Recording Projects: Sean Nos, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Recording Projects: Slow Airs and Set Dances, 1979/1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Recording Projects: Strings Attached, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Recording Projects: Terry Teahan and Gene Kelly, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Recording Projects: Three-Way Street, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Rego Records, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Riverdance, 1995-2000 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Rounder Records, 1976-2001 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Royalties, 1977-1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Saint Malachy's, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Saint Malachy's (Oversized), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 10)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: Clippings: Advertisements, 1987-1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: Articles, 1977-1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: General (folder one), 1973-1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: General (folder two), undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: Irish Echo, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: Irish Edition (folder one), 1989-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: Irish Edition (folder two), 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: Irish Voice, 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Says I, Says He: General, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Says I, Says He: Scripts (folder one), c. 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Says I, Says He: Scripts (folder two), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Session Directory, c.1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Set Lists, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Shanachie Entertainment Corp.: Correspondence, 1977-1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Shanachie Entertainment Corp.: Financials, 1977-1995, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Shenachie Entertainment Corp.: Mailings, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Shenachie Entertainment Corp.: Newsletters and Bulletins, 1976-c.1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Shenachie Entertainment Corp: Record Reviews, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Slane Music, 1975-1982 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Sleeve Notes, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Contracts, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: General (folder one), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: General (folder two), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: General (folder three), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: General (folder four), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Programs (folder one), 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Programs (folder two), 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Programs (folder three), 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Programs (folder four), 1994, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Tape Logs, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Festival of American Folklife: Tour, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Smithsonian Institution: General, 1982-1983, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Stamp Collecting, 1924-c.2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Swannanoa, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Tape Logs, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Tara Circle, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee Folklife Celebration, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee Folklore Society Bulletin (folder one), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Tennessee Folklore Society Bulletin (folder two), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee Folklore Society Bulletin (folder three), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Topic Records Ltd. (folder one), 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Topic Records Ltd. (folder two), 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Tory Island, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Traditional Music Magazine: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Transferred 78s: Logs, Correspondence, c. 1977 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Transatlantic Records Ltd., 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Travellers, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Vaudeville: Film Proposal, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Washington Irish Folk Festival, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Weaverville, CA., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Wolf Trap National Park for the Performing Arts (VA.): Folk Masters (folder one), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Wolf Trap National Park for the Performing Arts (VA.): Folk Masters (folder two), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Workshops, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - World Music Institute, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Audio-Visual Paperwork, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Budgets and Proposals, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Contacts, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Contracts and Agreements, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Field Notes, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Field Work: Brochures, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Field Work: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Folklife Report (folder one), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Folklife Report (folder two), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): General, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Resumes, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - World's Fair (1982: Knoxville, Tenn.): Staff Meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Series II: Individuals, 1879-2010; 5 boxes
  Series II: Individuals, 1879-2010 consists of materials collected by Dr. Moloney throughout the course of his academic and professional activities concerning specific individuals and groups. The majority of these individuals and groups are Irish or Irish-American, are closely associated with Irish traditional music, and often performers. Others are Irish or Irish-American academics, poets, and writers, including the Philadelphia-based historian Dennis Clark. Of particular note are materials related to Dr. Moloney himself that provide an insight into his private and public lives. Included in this series is a small set of materials given to Dr. Moloney by fiddler and radio host Tommy Caulfield, including ledger books, correspondence, radio receipts, advertisements, and concert programs which provide documentation on the Irish Musicians' Association and the Irish Musicians' Union in Philadelphia beginning in the 1940s.
  - Aliesan, Jody, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Altan, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Andrews, Gene, c. 1940 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bayes, Nora, 1973, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Black 47, 1992-2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Blanchette, Joseph, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Blaustein, Richard, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Blended Scotch, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bloom, Luka, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bothy Band, c. 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Boucicault, Dion, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)